ILGWU Education Department, Jasper Peyton Papers 5780/086
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Vermont Weekend, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Trip Information; routine
- Visitors. Foreign, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Why Education Is A Must In The ILGWU, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  pamphlet; routine
- Window Display, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  "Signature of 450,000"
- Women, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous, 1976-1982 (Box 10, Folder 8-13)
- Photos (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Series II: General Executive Board (G.E.B.) Reports., 1967-1976 (Box 11)
  Scope Note: This series includes Educational Reports to the G.E.B., Educational Activities Reports, Correspondence, questionnaires, and routine paperwork.
- G.E.B., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- G.E.B., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2-7)
- G.E.B., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8-11)
- G.E.B., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 12-18)
- G.E.B. [folders 1-5 of 10], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19-23)
- G.E.B. [folders 6-10 of 10], 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
- G.E.B., 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9-18)
- G.E.B., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 19-21)
- G.E.B., 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1-11)
- AFL-CIO, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Includes "Galaxy Conference on Reaching the Union Member"
- AFL-CIO, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- American Red Cross (ARC), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  "First Aid Training in Business and Industry"
- American Veterans Committee (AVC), 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Outgoing Letters
- Art Program for Union Members (APUM), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Proposal
- The Fashion Group, Incorporated, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Bulletin
- Miscellany, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Various newsletters and advertisements
- Invoices, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Book Inventory, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Pamphlet Request Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Pamphlet Requests for "Education is a Must", 1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Pamphlet Request Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Films on File Request, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Information Requests, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Pamphlet Requests for "Welcome", 1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  In English
- Pamphlet Requests for "Welcome", 1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  In Spanish
- Pamphlet Requests for "Welcome", 1973 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  In Greek
- Pamphlet Requests for "Welcome", 1973 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  In Italian
- Pamphlet Requests for "Welcome", 1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  In French
- Pamphlet Requests for "Welcome", 1973 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  In Chinese
- Pamphlet Requests for "Welcome" Correspondence, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Requested languages for "Welcome" were not available.
- Pamphlet Requests for "Welcome" Correspondence, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Requested languages for "Welcome" were available.
- Pamphlet Requests for "Welcome" Correspondence, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  Requested languages for "Welcome" were all available.
- Pamphlet Requests, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Inventory and Pending Requests
- Newsletters, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Various newsletters and reports.
- Pamphlet Request Correspondence, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Specifically for an Italian version of "Welcome" for Canadians
- Naturalization and Citizenship, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  Requests, Outgoing Letters, and various other material on the subject of naturalizing and educating immigrants.
- Advanced Labor Leadership Conference Book, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  Book from a one week seminar held by the Education Department of the Texas AFL-CIO
- College and University Calendars, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  Calendars and schedules of events, such as conferences and seminars, held on college campuses
- College and University Incoming Letters, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Committee of Political Education (COPE), 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Community Relations Newsletters, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Various community publications
- National Working Conference on Reaching the Union Member, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Consumer Assembly Committees, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- 6th Annual New York Consumer Assembly, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Convention, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Scholarship, Training, Education, and Political (STEP), 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Continuing Education, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Continuing education through Cortina language courses, Open Doors business courses, and other courses, conferences, and seminars.
- Death Benefit Fund Report, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Departmental Notices, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  List of locals, joint boards, joint councils area offices and subordinate organizations
- Educational Direction Outgoing Letters, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- English Classes, 1970-1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Foreign Visitors, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Biographies of foreign visitors
- Foreign Visitors, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Various Materials Regarding Education, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Pamphlets, Letters, Invoices
- Information Requests, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Various reports
- General Elections Board, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  Various letters and reports
- Health Care, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  Brochures
- Information Requests Correspondence, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- New Member Applications, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- New Member Applications, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Affiliation Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Invoices, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Research Material Request, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  Graduate student requests information for thesis.
- Knit Good News, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  Newsletter
- Invoices, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Book Divisions, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Book Divisions, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Political Files, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Labor Songs, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Requests for "Joe Glazer Sings Labor Songs."
- Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  Research Department Report
- Labor Songs, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Scholarship Fund, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Includes a copy of a report from the "Selections Committee Meeting National Scholarship Fund"
- Scholarship Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  General information, and includes a folder of the list of past scholarship winners.
- Scholarship Fund, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Includes a copy of the report "Selections Committee Meeting National Scholarship Fund" of that year.
- Scholarship, Training, Education, and Political (STEP), 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  Newsletters, requests for publications, and correspondence.
- Scholarship, Training, Education, and Political (STEP), 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  Newsletters and correspondence.
- Scholarship, Training, Education, and Political (STEP), 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  Correspondence
- Labor Songs (Box 16, Folder 14)
  Sheet Music
- Black Cultural and Business Exposition, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  Letter to Jasper Peyton
- Surveys, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  Survey called "How to Reach the Union Member"
- Travel Information, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  Pamphlets
- Travel Information, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Travel Information, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Gus Tyler Outgoing Letters, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  Tyler sending information of interest to various affiliates.
- University Letters, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Documents, Newsletters, Pamphlets, Announcements, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  Dealing with education
- Miscellaneous Documents, Newsletters, Pamphlets, Announcements, 1971-1978 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Documents, Newsletters, Pamphlets, Announcements, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  Book catalogues
- Publisher's Weekly, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  The Book Industry Journal
- Publisher's Weekly, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Stalinism, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Contains two handbooks "Titoism vs Stalinism" and "The Citizen's Handbook on Stalinism."
- Slave Labor, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Handbooks in both English and Russian
- Slave Labor, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Handbooks in different foreign languages.
- Photographs (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Three photographs.